// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I came _____ America.",
    answer: "from",
    options: [
      "from",
      "at",
      "in",
      "on"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I ____ cold.",
    answer: "Have",
    options: [
      "am",
      "is",
      "had",
      "Have"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "________ car is very old fashioned.",
    answer: "Fatima’s ",
    options: [
      "Fatima’s ",
      "Fatima is",
      "Fatimas ",
      "Fatimas'"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "I speak English but he_______.",
    answer: "doesn’t speak  ",
    options: [
      "doesn't speaks ",
      " speaks",
      "don't speak",
      "doesn’t speak "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Nowadays everyone ______ internet.",
    answer: "use",
    options: [
      "use",
      "uses",
      "used",
      "had used"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "______ there anybody in the room?",
    answer: "Is",
    options: [
      "Are",
      "Is",
      "Am",
     "If"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many siblings ________?",
    answer: "do you have",
    options: [
      "do you have",
      "have you gotten",
      "did you had",
     "both A & B"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What___ you doing?",
    answer: "are",
    options: [
      "is",
      "are",
      "am",
     "if"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb:9 ,
    question: " Which book is ______?",
    answer: "your's",
    options: [
      "your",
      "your's",
      "yours",
     "your is"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "She is____ home.",
    answer: "at",
    options: [
      "in",
      "on",
      "at",
     "from"
   ]
  },

  /*you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: ,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },*/
];